<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DummyApp</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyA2b1cZXleSVDWFEpe9jknNNUmI9e7uYOA</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1399687486755645</string>
    <string name="third">Another excellent use of the CoordinatorLayout is with the CollapsingToolbar and Appbar. The CollapsingToolbar is another of the amazing features of the Android Support Design Library. For this activity, we are going to build a layout with a FAB that is anchored
        to the Appbar. The FAB scrolls with the AppbarAnother excellent use of the CoordinatorLayout is with the CollapsingToolbar and Appbar. The CollapsingToolbar is another of the amazing features of the Android Support Design Library. For this activity, we are going to build a layout with a FAB that is anchored
        to the Appbar. The FAB scrolls with the Appbar, and disappears when the Appbar is collapsed., and disappears when the Appbar is collapsed.</string>
    <string name="second">Another excellent use of the CoordinatorLayout is with the CollapsingToolbar and Appbar. The CollapsingToolbar is another of the amazing features of the Android Support Design Library. For this activity, we are going to build a layout with
        a FAB that is anchored toAnother excellent use of the CoordinatorLayout is with the CollapsingToolbar and Appbar. The CollapsingToolbar is another of the amazing features of the Android Support Design Library. For this activity, we are going to build a layout with a FAB that is
        anchored to the Appbar. The FAB scrolls with the Appbar, and disappears when the Appbar is collapsed. the Appbar. The FAB scrolls with the Appbar, and disappears when the Appbar is collapsed.</string>
    <string name="first">Another excellent use of the CoordinatorLayout is with the CollapsingToolbar and Appbar. The CollapsingToolbar is another of the amazing features of the Android Support Design Library. For this activity, we are going to build a layout with a FAB
        that is anchored to the Appbar. The FAB scrolls with the Appbar, and disappears when the Appbar is collapsedAnother excellent use of the CoordinatorLayout is with the CollapsingToolbar and Appbar. The CollapsingToolbar is another of the amazing features of the Android Support Design Library. For this activity, we are going to build a layout with a FAB that is anchored to the Appbar.
        The FAB scrolls with the Appbar, and disappears when the Appbar is collapsed..</string>
</resources>
